[Music]
Anara Dekhan S 24 Inse
News To Ever
Over
10 Lakh In 10 Years Become In Another Bum
And Kriye There Is No Limit So There Is
Immediate Peace Of Mind Customer Today Policy Taken
10 Lakh By Premium Capacity In A Due
Course Of 10 Years When Actually Ko Claim Lena Hai
High Value Gain Till Then I Will Have To Apply
It With Let's Explain Suppose 10 Lakh
Sum Assured Customer Has And There Is An Unusual
Event Of Cancer That Is Therapy
Required And Multiple Admissions Required And
In That Case The Expenses Could Exceed
10 Lakh During The Year That Time The
Customer Can Say That I Will Exercise The
Option Of Infa Care And For One Time I
Can Take A High Value So Its A Wonderful
Power With The Customer There Is No Capping A
38 Lakh Claim Aa Gaya A 10 Lakh That
Extra 28 Lakh  will be paid under this
policy right and if it is a regular policy
and any other policy in the market this power
or this feature is not there 28 lakh will have to be some info care
for you very very
strong
feature if some like a said demographic
what is needed is 5 lakh some 10 lakh some the pin code
and the location where the customer is coming from the
cost of care the additional coverage and the
recommended so this all is packed into the AI
feature and this is giving us super and it comes
to elite this is a small
video and 180 days then you have reset
benefit of you know if your 10 lakh some 2
lakh used then that 2 lakh also gets covered
and your sum is reset at 10 lakh so this is all
guaranteed benefit which we will speak
of again now on the slide you can see lock score
of the domestic and ye sab jo hai aajkal ke tareekh mein daj r
Kind of features are
mandatory so those are some of the features which are
in the slide they are inbuilt and before that
what we saw are the add-on slide so add-on
features said our product when we went on the
drawing board we thought we wanted to
make a very innovative product so then we talked
about three to four features which are
extremely innovative and we spoke about that but
one extremely important element
that we have brought in this product is
the artificial intelligence thing we have a
rich database we have a rich understanding
of the customers who have health insurance
through us not only through retail but also through
group basis that we have said that let's
look at features which are extremely
close to this customer segment so we have
broken it down into many segments
based on age based on the family size based on the
pin code from where the customer is coming what is the
requirement, how much does he want to spend on
this basis  We have a past history, we
have a way to map that against what the
requirements could be of this customer and
given artificial intelligence output. The
beauty of this is that it is extremely close
to what a customer would ideally want, so that's the
intent. We give a whole sum cover to
the product, whatever his requirements are, so that
we can present it completely. Because there are
22 Advance Plus in this
product, we are trying to make a package that will seem extremely
attractive to the
customer. From that perspective, what has been done is that there is a
five-year age bracket beyond which the
premium changes. So, suppose let me give you an
example, I am 25 years old, right now
I enter into elevation till the age of 30, my
premium will remain the same. As I turn 31,
that premium will change. So, that is a
natural thing that happens in most of the  The
product in the market is
called 'CHAR', like age bracket changes, it is not every
year but the
premium changes in the age bracket of five years. So, the
unlimited coverage is this feature, we can make it
available through three or four features in this product or we can offer it to any customer, the
customer can take it, firstly, the base
product itself can be taken unlimited, as
I told you, the products in the product market today, some
say my
maximum sum assured is Rs 1 crore, some say my maximum sum assured is Rs 9 crore,
some say my maximum sum
assured is Rs 1 crore, in Elevate we have kept unlimited sum assured
in the base, so this is one way the
customer can take unlimited sum assured, so he has
complete peace of mind. Another way is that the
customer says I want to buy a Rs 10
lakh sum assured, okay, you take a sum assured of Rs 10 lakh,
along with that I will take Infa Care, so
as I explained, what is Infa Care,
one claim up to Infa amount the
customer can take during this policy.  So that's another way
of availing insurance that I will take
a sum assured of Rs 10 lakh and I can claim up to any
value insurance. So this is the second
way, then there is the power booster, which
I explained that the power booster will
increase your insurance by 100% every year and there is no
limit of up to it, it is up to infinity.
So these are two or three elements in Elevate where the
customer's insurance is infinity, in the
base product and insurance and
power. It is very
difficult to tell from where the premium starts.
You might want to hear that it
starts from Rs 3000. It is not like that, so the
entry product price starts from Rs 215 for the
customer and if you look at the various
pin codes and customers going to different
cities, but let's assure you that the pricing of the
product is extremely comparatively done,
where we have mapped it with
competing products and we have seen that the
Its pricing is excellent, so if
any customer goes to buy it himself or compares it,
who has understanding, they will love to see
the pricing of this product, so we have
insured that the product is strong and the
pricing is also excellent.